Poughkeepsie Postcard and Flyer Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Poughkeepsie Postcard and Flyer Collection
1904-1944
1888-1953
npkmc-237-261
1 Linear Foot 2 Boxes
Postcard production and popularity in the U.S. erupted in the 1890s and early 1900s. This is demonstrated in the collection, with a majority of the postcards hailing from the first half of the twentieth century. Postcards served as a fast and easy way to communicate with peers and loved ones at the time.This collection consists of postcards and some flyers from the Hudson Valley region of New York with most depicting places and things in Poughkeepsie, New York. The collection includes both blank and used postal cards, the bulk of which are from the first half of the twentieth century (1904-1944). Undated postcards in the collection are also presumably from the twentieth century.
Marist College Archives and Special Collections 3399 North Road Poughkeepsie, NY Poughkeepsie New York 12601 United States
Individuals requesting reproductions expressly assume the responsibility for compliance with all pertinent provisions of the Copyright Act, 17 U.S.C. ss101 et seq. Patrons further agree to indemnify and hold harmless the Marist College Archives & Special Collections and its staff in connection with any disputes arising from the Copyright Act, over the reproduction of material at the request of patrons. For more information please visit the following website: https://www.loc.gov/copyright/title17/.
Although postcards were circulating in the United States by the 1870s, postcard production and popularity in the U.S. particularly took off in the 1890s and early 1900s. This is demonstrated in the collection, with a majority of the postcards hailing from the first half of the twentieth century. Postcards served as a fast and easy way to communicate with peers and loved ones at the time. In 1898, private printing companies were finally allowed to produce postcards in contrast to previous government control, contributing to their flourishing. As is demonstrated in the collection, from 1901 to 1907, standard postcards only had room for addresses on the back, leaving little room for messaging since pictures were on the front side. This changed in 1907 when the divided back was introduced, leaving space for a message on one side of the back and the address on the other. From 1907 to 1915, “Real photo” postcards started to gain more traction, rather than the typical drawing-based postcard. By the mid-twentieth century, postcards were produced and used in much smaller quantities, and most postcards seen in this era through today are called photochrom postcards; photograph postcards in color and with a particular sheen.
Up until the first World War, German printers dominated the postcard market, with an abundance of early cards in this particular collection reading “Printed in Germany.” Many of the postcards in this collection were produced by the Ruben Publishing Co. out of Newburgh, New York. Jacob Ruben, a Russian-American émigré, opened a stationary business in Newburgh in 1906, and also became a well-known Hudson Valley area commercial photographer. Ruben’s popular photographic tourist postcards of the Poughkeepsie area can be seen in this collection. Other publishers include John B. Flagler of Poughkeepsie, N.Y. (although printed in Germany), Kingston News Service, and the Rotograph Company. The Rotograph Co. was a publisher and printer of postcards based in New York that was an American offshoot of the German photograph and postcard publishers, Neue Photographische Gesellschaft.
This collection consists of postcards and some flyers from the Hudson Valley region of New York with most more specifically depicting places and things in Poughkeepsie, New York. The collection includes both blank and used postal cards, the bulk of which are from the first half of the twentieth century (1904-1944). Undated postcards in the collection are also presumably from the twentieth century. The postcards which contain writing were sent, created, and received by a wide variety of individuals. A few repeating names on the postcards include Miss Anna Dunn, Miss Florence Davidson, and Mrs. Simpson. Business flyer advertisements from local Poughkeepsie establishments are included.
Postcards; Hudson River Valley (N.Y. and N.J.); Poughkeepsie (N.Y.)
The postcards are divided into series based on subject and are arranged alphabetically by place/theme within each subject series. This collection is organized into thirteen series: Vassar College; Businesses and Buildings; Clubs/Homes/Societies; Hospitals; Civil War Memorials; Schools; Churches; Streets; Bridges, Boats, and the Hudson River; Parks; Fire Companies; General Poughkeepsie; and Business Advertisements.
Collection was donated to the Marist College Archives & Special Collection.
No accruals are expected.
McCann Post Card Collection
- 1. Vassar College, 1904-1943
  - Belle Skinner Hall of Music, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Chapel Across the Lake, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-05-03 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Chapel Across the Lake, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-02-25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1943-09-25 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - [Chapel, Vassar College], 1910-11-01 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - The Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - The Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Interior of Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1915-12-23 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - New Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - New Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - New Chapel, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Thompson Chapel (Vassar College). Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Thompson Chapel (Vassar College). Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Vassar Chapel, 1908-11-04 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Vassar Chapel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-06-04 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Vassar Chapel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Vassar Elm Walk From Chapel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1922-09-28 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Conservatory, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-06-22 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. The Conservatory, Vassar College., Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Vassar Conservatory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Daisy Chain, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Davison Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Dormitories, Vassar College, 1905-03-02 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Entrance to Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Vassar College Entrance, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-06-26 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Vassar College Entrance. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Floral Circle and Students’ Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - The Graduating Class, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - The Graduating Class, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-03-08 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Gymnasium, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Gymnasium, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - The Gymnasium, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Alumni Gymnasium, Vassar College, 1910-11-05 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Swift Infirmary, Vassar College., 1912-09-15 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Vassar Infirmary, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-06-08 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Jewett Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - “Jewett Hall”, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Josselyn Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Josselyn Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1943-08-11 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Kendrick Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Lathrop Hall, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-06-07 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Interior of Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Library and Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-02-18 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Library Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1937-07-12 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-09-07 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - The Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Main Entrance, Thompson Library & Left Wing, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-08-22 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Thomson Memorial Library, 1911-08 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Thompson Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Thompson Memorial Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1932-08-30 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Thompson Memorial Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Thompson Memorial Library, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Vassar College Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Vassar Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Vassar Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - The Lodge, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - The Lodge, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-05-31 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Back of Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - The Main Building at Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1921-09-14 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Main Building, Vassar College. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Main Building, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1924-04-05 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Main Building], Undated (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Vassar May Pole, 1910, Photo by Fay, 1910-05-12 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - The Museum. Vassar College., Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Museum, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Museum, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - North Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-11-17 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - North Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1913-09-27 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Observatory, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-07-24 (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Observatory, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Observatory, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-08-14 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Presidents Home - Vassar, 1908-11 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - The President’s Residence, Vassar College, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - The President’s Residence, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, 1904 (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 85)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 86)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 87)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 88)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-06-15 (Box 1, Folder 89)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905-08-03 (Box 1, Folder 90)
  - Rockefeller Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-09-07 (Box 1, Folder 91)
  - Strong Dormitory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-05-24 (Box 1, Folder 92)
  - Strong Hall, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 93)
  - Strong Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 94)
  - The Walk to Sunset Hill, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-12-06 (Box 1, Folder 95)
  - Taylor Hall and Main Entrance Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 96)
  - Taylor Hall and Main Entrance Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 97)
  - Taylor Hall and Main Entrance Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 98)
  - Taylor Hall, Vassar College, Undated (Box 1, Folder 99)
  - Taylor Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 100)
  - Taylor Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 101)
  - Taylor Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 102)
  - Taylor Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 103)
  - Taylor Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 104)
  - Taylor's Hall, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 105)
  - Vassar College, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 106)
  - Vassar Inn, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 107)
  - Vassar Institute. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 108)
  - Vassar Institute, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-10-28 (Box 1, Folder 109)
  - The Lake Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Vassar Lake], 1912-07-23 (Box 1, Folder 110)
  - Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y. [Vassar Lake], Undated (Box 1, Folder 111)
  - Vassar Lake and Drive. Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905-07-10 (Box 1, Folder 112)
  - Vassar Lake and the Willows, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-02-04 (Box 1, Folder 113)
  - Vassar Lake, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-12-01 (Box 1, Folder 114)
  - Vassar Lake Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-02 (Box 1, Folder 115)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-10-10 (Box 1, Folder 116)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-07-20 (Box 1, Folder 117)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 118)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-07-09 (Box 1, Folder 119)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 120)
  - Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 121)
  - Vassar Lake, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 122)
  - Vassar Lake, Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-01-06 (Box 1, Folder 123)
  - “The Willows,” Vassar Lake, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-08-13 (Box 1, Folder 124)
- 2. Businesses and Buildings, 1904-1944
  - Adriance Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905-11-22 (Box 1, Folder 125)
  - Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 126)
  - Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-10-02 (Box 1, Folder 127)
  - Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1926-07-21 (Box 1, Folder 128)
  - Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1904 (Box 1, Folder 129)
  - Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 130)
  - The Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 131)
  - The Adriance Memorial Library, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-17 (Box 1, Folder 132)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Adriance Memorial Library, 1909-10-31 (Box 1, Folder 133)
  - Commemorating the American Bicentennial, 1776-1996, Beekman Arms Hotel, “Oldest Hotel in America”, Rhinebeck, New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 134)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 135)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1909-01-01 (Box 1, Folder 136)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1905 (Box 1, Folder 137)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 138)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-07-01 (Box 1, Folder 139)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 140)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 141)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 142)
  - Dutchess County Court House. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 143)
  - Dutchess County – Office Building, Undated (Box 1, Folder 144)
  - Fallkill Building. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 145)
  - F.I.A.T. Motor Factory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 146)
  - The Franklin D. Roosevelt Library Hyde Park, New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 147)
  - Hotel Campbell, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1944-08-20 (Box 1, Folder 148)
  - Hotel Campbell, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 149)
  - Hotel Campbell, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 150)
  - IBM International Business Machine Corp. Main Plant & Subsidiary Buildings South Road, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 151)
  - IBM Main Plant, Education Center, Country Club, Undated (Box 1, Folder 152)
  - King’s Court Hotel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1939-02-23 (Box 1, Folder 153)
  - [Lindmark’s New and Antiquarian Bookseller] “Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Claims fame for three things: Vassar College, Smith Brothers Cough Drops and Lindmark’s” (N.Y. Herald-Tribune), Undated (Box 1, Folder 154)
  - Luckey, Platt & Co., Poughkeepsie’s Leading Store. 26 Departments., 1909-10-02 (Box 1, Folder 155)
  - Interior of Moore Brother’s Store, 231 Main St., Poughkeepsie’s Leading Shoe House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 156)
  - Municipal Building New Market Street Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 157)
  - New York Central Passenger Station, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 158)
  - Court House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1916-10-30 (Box 1, Folder 159)
  - Post Office, Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 160)
  - Post Office, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 161)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Post Office and Dutchess County Court House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 162)
  - U.S. Post Office Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 163)
  - United States Post Office Poughkeepsie, New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 164)
  - Conservatory and Plant Room, The “Saltford Flower Shop”, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-22 (Box 1, Folder 165)
  - Plant Room. The Saltford Flower Shop, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 166)
  - The Saltford Flower Shop. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 167)
  - 134 No. Hamilton St. – Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Home of the Smith Brothers’ Black and Menthol Cough Drops and Triple Action Cough Syrup, Undated (Box 1, Folder 168)
  - Smith Brothers Candy Counter and Luncheonette, Undated (Box 1, Folder 169)
  - Smith Brothers Restaurant, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 170)
  - Stratford Theatre, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 171)
  - Stratford Theatre, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1922-10-21 (Box 1, Folder 172)
  - [Unnamed Poughkeepsie Building], 1905-11-05 (Box 1, Folder 173)
  - Van’s Garage. Poughkeepsie, N.Y. 14-16-18-20-24 Catharine Street., Undated (Box 1, Folder 174)
  - The Windsor Hotel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 175)
- 3. Clubs/Homes/Societies, 1906-1930
  - Amrita Club, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 176)
  - Amrita Club, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-10-14 (Box 1, Folder 177)
  - Armory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 178)
  - The Armory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-01 (Box 1, Folder 179)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. State Armory, Undated (Box 1, Folder 180)
  - State Armory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 181)
  - State Armory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1927-09-14 (Box 1, Folder 182)
  - State Armory, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 183)
  - Clinton House, Poughkeepsie, New York, Undated (Box 1, Folder 184)
  - Commemorating the American Bicentennial, 1776-1976, Clinton House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 185)
  - The Old Governor Clinton Mansion, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1911-02-19 (Box 1, Folder 186)
  - Dutchess Golf and Country Club, Undated (Box 1, Folder 187)
  - Elks and Knights of Columbus Bldgs., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 188)
  - Elks and Knights of Columbus Bldgs., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 189)
  - Elks and Knights of Columbus Bldgs., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 190)
  - Gallaudet Home for Deaf Mutes. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-07-20 (Box 1, Folder 191)
  - Knights of Columbus Hall, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 192)
  - Christian Science Society, Masonic Temple, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 193)
  - Masonic Temple, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-08-19 (Box 1, Folder 194)
  - Grill Room, Morgan House, Carl H.F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 195)
  - Japanese Garden at the Morgan House, Carl H. F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 196)
  - Morgan House, Carl H.F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 197)
  - Morgan House Dining Room, C.H.F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 198)
  - Morgan House Office, C.H.F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-09-25 (Box 1, Folder 199)
  - Morgan House Pompeiian Room Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 200)
  - Morgan House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 201)
  - Morgan House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 202)
  - Morgan House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-10-05 (Box 1, Folder 203)
  - The Morgan House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 204)
  - Parlor. Morgan House, Carl H.F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 205)
  - Parlor. Morgan House, Carl H.F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-02-12 (Box 1, Folder 206)
  - Pompeiian Room, **Morgan House**, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1913-10-01 (Box 1, Folder 207)
  - Reading Room. **Morgan House**, Carl H. F. Kohl, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 208)
  - Nelson House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 209)
  - The Nelson House Horatio N. Bain, Prop. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 210)
  - Nelson House Hotel, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 211)
  - Nelson House, Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-02-03 (Box 1, Folder 212)
  - The Nelson House, Market Street, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-08-11 (Box 1, Folder 213)
  - Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 214)
  - Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1906-11-21 (Box 1, Folder 215)
  - Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1930-04-26 (Box 1, Folder 216)
  - Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 217)
  - Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 218)
  - Nelson House, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 219)
  - Nelson House. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 220)
  - The Nelson House, Walter Averill, Prop., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 221)
  - Poughkeepsie, N.Y. Nelson House, Undated (Box 1, Folder 222)
  - Old Ladies Home, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 223)
  - Old Men’s Home, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1912-03-21 (Box 1, Folder 224)
  - Poughkeepsie Tennis Club, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1907-11 (Box 1, Folder 225)
  - Poughkeepsie Yacht Club, 1907-06-07 (Box 1, Folder 226)
  - Poughkeepsie Yacht Club House, 1909-07-15 (Box 1, Folder 227)
  - Prindel Home for Retired Editors, &c., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1910-06-25 (Box 1, Folder 228)
  - The Pringle Home for Aged Literary Men, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1908-10 (Box 1, Folder 229)
  - Pringle Home for Aged Literary Men. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 230)
  - Pringle Home for Aged Literary Men. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1911-03-17 (Box 1, Folder 231)
  - Symphony Society, Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 232)
  - Vassar Home for Aged Men. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1910-09-28 (Box 1, Folder 233)
  - Vassar Home for Aged Men. Poughkeepsie, N.Y., 1914-02-03 (Box 1, Folder 234)
  - Y.M.C.A., Poughkeepsie, N.Y., Undated (Box 1, Folder 235)